Guide to the Lester R. Armstrong Photographs circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Lester R. Armstrong Photographs
circa 1917-1957
Whitman College and Northwest Archives 345 Boyer Avenue Walla Walla, WA 99362 Archives@whitman.edu https://library.whitman.edu/archives/
Armstrong, Lester R.
WCMss.067
6.3 linear feet 5 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, 1 small flat box
Lester R. Armstrong was a professional photographer who operated out of Walla Walla, Washington. This collection contains his negatives, dating from circa 1917 to 1957, which primarily document life in Walla Walla, including portraits, town events, and buildings.
Collection is open for research.
Donated to the Whitman College and Northwest Archives in 1978. There is no known accession information associated with this collection.
Lester Randall Armstrong was born on July 30, 1894 in Farnhamville, Iowa. He moved to Walla Walla in 1900 with his mother and two siblings, after his father died. During World War I, he served with the 1st Division at Fort Lewis.
Armstrong married Myrtle Zimmerman in 1926, and operated a sign business in town for 14 years. He also worked at the McCaw General Hospital during World War Two. When the war ended, Armstrong opened up a photography business, Armstrong Photos, out of his house, which he operated until 1951. Then, he worked as a photographer for the Walla Walla Office of the United States Army Corps of Engineers. Lester Armstrong died on May 2, 1955.
The Lester R. Armstrong photographs consist primarily of negatives documenting portraits, family events, and scenes of Walla Walla, Washington, dating from circa 1917 to 1957. Notably, there are scenes from the United Service Organization (U.S.O) events, and McCaw General Hospital, which depict activities during World War Two. While the bulk of the collection was produced from Lester's professional photography studio, Armstrong Photos, portions of the collection are dated from before and after he was operating this business.
Whitman College
Walla Walla (Wash.)--Social life and customs
Photographers--Washington (State)--20th century
- 35 mm [Wrestling?], Undated (Box 4, Folder 1468)
- A. M. Jensen: Exteriors, 1951 July 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- A. M. Jensen: Nylon pajama display, 1950 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- A. M. Jensen: Show windows for display, 1950 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Abbott printed, 1942 March (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Accepted photographs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Advertising, self, 1948 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Aerial: Dixie, Mill Creek, etcetera, 1950 July 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Aerial: Over Walla Walla, Circa 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Aerial: Seven-thousand feet, 1950 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Aerial: Trailer Town, McNary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Aerial: Veterans hospital and McCaw, Circa 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Aero test, 1948 October (Box 1, Folder 9)
- [African American: Baby], Undated (Box 1, Folder 345)
- [African American: Lewis, Lizzie], 1944 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 346)
- [African American: Portraits], Undated (Box 1, Folder 347)
- [African American: Portraits], Undated (Box 1, Folder 344)
- Agate column, Depoe Bay, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Aibiour [Aubian], Wayne, 1948 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Air Base Walla Walla: Sergeant Hogen, Sargeant Sidellas, Corporate De Mougin, 1944 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Air Base Walla Walla: Sergeant Hogen, Sergeant Sidellas, Corporate De Mougin, Undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Air Show: Walla Walla, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Air Tour: Tri-State Mayer Riley of Portland, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Air view: Over Locust street, Circa 1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Air views: At fair, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Air views: Over city, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Akridge, PVT.: WAC Copeland, Peggy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1512)
- Alexander, Elmer L., 1948 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Allard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Alley, 628 Locust street, 1954 March (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Alligators, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- America on Parade, backstage, 1941 July 4 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American Legion Banquet, first at hall, Circa 1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American Legion, poppy window, 1948 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Anderson, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Anderson Grocery, Walla Walla: Refrigerated meat counter, 1951 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Anderson, C.C., Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Anderson, C.C.: A. M. Jensen, 1950 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Anderson, C.C.: Bathing suit display: A. M. Jensen, bathing girl window, 1948 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Anderson, C.C.: Coca-cola display, 1947 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Anderson, C.C.: Copies of ad layouts, 1948 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Anderson, C.C.: Dickey shirts, 1951 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Anderson, C.C.: Easter window, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Anderson, C.C.: Furniture department, interior, 1948 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Anderson, C.C.: Window displays, 1948 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Anderson, C.C.: Window displays: A. M. Jensen, 1949 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Anderson, C.C.: WIndow displays: A. M. Jensen Company, 1948 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Anderson, C.C.: Windows displays, furs, 1946 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Anderson, Clarence Family, 1947 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Anderson, Profesor at Whitman College and Professor Dale of University of Idaho, 1946 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Anderson, Ruth, 1949 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Annual Walla Walla Purebred Breeders Association Show and Sale, Circa 1948 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Archer, 1944 May (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Arentz, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Arentz, Captain, 1943 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Arentz: Old folks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Arlington, Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Armstrong Circus, Undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Armstrong Circus, Undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Army, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Army, Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Army, Circa 1918 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Ashford, Edward C.: Fishing at Sekiu, 1951 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Ashworth, Anna, 1943 November (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Ashworth, Anna: Farewell party, 1947 December (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Ashworth, Anna: Party, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Astoria, Circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Astoria harbor views, 1949 August (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Astoria, Oregon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Atwood, Robert: Baby, 1947 December (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Aubian, Wayne, 1951 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Aubian, Wayne: Residence, 1949 June 1 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Audrey, 1945 January 1 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Auto races: Model T, Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Auto races: Walla Walla, 1940 June (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Autos, Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Aviation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Aviation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Aviation:, 1940 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Aviation: Air circus, air show in Walla Walla, 1947 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Aviation: Army bomber, 1939 October (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Aviation: Model meet, Circa 1939 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Aviation: Model sheet, Circa 1939 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Aviation: Tri State Air Town, airplane tour, 1947 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Babcock, Claire, 1948 September 20 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Bachstein, John: Whitman Beta Beta Phi, 1948 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Bachtold: Baby, 811 College Ave, 1947 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Backhouse, Undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Backhouse: Meacham, Oregon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Baird, Sargeant, Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Band in Unidentified Location], Circa 1940 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Band: College of Idaho during Whitman College homecoming, Marcus Whitman Hotel, 1947 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Band: Pasadena Tournament of roses band, Walla Walla, 1940 June (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Band: Ted Fio Rito, Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Bandon? Oregon, 1942 or 1952 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Banquet: Alpha Chi Alumni, 1950 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Banquet: Wagon Wheelers, 1946 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Banquet: Walla Walla County employees, 1947 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Barber, 1949 November 17 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Barber and tax collector: Hayes, 1987 October (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Barrie, Jack, Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Basketball: Homecoming, Pasco High School, 1947 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Baslee, Allen, 1952 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Baslee, Allen, Undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Basta, Reitha, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Bastron, Leroy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Bastron, Leroy, 1949 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Bastron, Leroy, 1949 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Batteforina, Undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Baughman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Baylan, Baby, 1947 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Beach: Neah Bay, Olympic Peninsula, Washington: Cattle on beach, Undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Beach: Neah Bay, Washington, Circa 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1777)
- Beach: Ruby: Taken from near Destruction Island, Olympic Peninsula, Washington, Undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Beach: Venice Beach, California, Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Beatty, J. J.: Christmas pictures, 1946 December 24 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Becker Motors: Burbee candy truck, 1948 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Becker Motors: Davis Kaiser truck, 1949 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Becker Motors: Exteriors, 1946 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Becker Motors: Laundry truck, 1949 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Becker Motors: Marcus Whitman truck, 1949 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Becker Motors: singles, 1949 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Becker Motors: Young's Dairy, 1949 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Becker, Associated, 1949 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Becker: Launch, 1949 June (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Beet harvesting: Portland Co-operative, 1949 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Bellingham, Washington, Undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Bench Work, Undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Benton: Mrs. Geo: Daughters, Circa 1942 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Beon, Morris: Baby, 1947 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Bergevin, Clem, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Bergevin, Clem: Arabian horse, Swabie, Undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Bergevin, Clem: Bull and herd branch, Circa 1955 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Bergevin, Clem: Bust shots, Undated (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Bergevin, Clem: Cattle and Bull, 1947 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 125.2)
- Bergevin, Clem: Horses, Walla Walla County Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Bergevin, Clem: Picture at rodeo, 1948 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 125.6)
- Bergevin, Clem: Ranch, cattle tour, 1949 June (Box 1, Folder 125.5)
- Bergevin, Clem: Running horse, 1947 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Bergevin, Clem: Swabie with saddle, Undated (Box 1, Folder 125.1)
- Bergevin, Clem: Western Livestock Journal tour, 1947 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 125.3)
- Bergevin, Clem: Western Livestock Journal tour, 1948 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 125.4)
- Bergevin, Clem: White mule and stud, Undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Bergevin, De Mosse: Children, 1945 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Bergevin, De Mosse: Horse, 1947 October (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Bergevin, De Mosse: Rodeo, 1947 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Bergevin, De Mosse: Rodeo, 1947 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- Bergevin, De Mosse: Rodeo at ranch, 1946 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Bergevin, Mrs. Clem: At Lowden, 1948 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Bill poster, Undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Bird and birdhouse, Undated (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Bird: Crow on head, Undated (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Bird: On Camera, Undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Birdeye Snyder Company: Defective beams, 1946 September 5 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Bleakney, Dr.: Family Group, Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Bleakney: Fiftieth Anniversary, 1946 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Blossoms: Cottonwood, Undated (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Boat, United States Coast Guard: Port Angeles, Washington, 1949 August (Box 5, Folder 1779)
- Boat: At Depoe Bay, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Boat: Fishing: Owner, J. K. Francisco, 1949 August (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Boat: Freightner, Undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Boat: Italian, Undated (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Boat: Luckenbach, Circa 1936 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Boat: Luckenbach: San Francisco Bay, Undated (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Boat: Model, Undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Boat: Passenger, Undated (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Boat: Speed, Undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Boat: Toy: Nelson Whitman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Boat: Tug, Undated (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Boat: Yachts: Portland, Oregon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Boating: Priest Lake, Idaho, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1795)
- Boats, sports, and fishing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Boats, Trawlers: Depoe Bay, Oregon: Sunset, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1817)
- Bogard, Dr., Undated (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Boiler Bay, Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1801)
- Boise, Undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Bond drive, Undated (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Bonfire, Undated (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Bonneville, Undated (Box 1, Folder 155)
- Bontrop, Mrs., 1944 May (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Book Nook, 1940 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Book Nook: Brown and Wanda, Undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Botta, Mr. and Mrs., Undated (Box 1, Folder 159)
- Boy with balloon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Boy with toy boat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Boys swimming, Undated (Box 1, Folder 162)
- Braden, James and family, 1948 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 163)
- Bridge: Covered, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 167)
- Bridge: Covered: Oregon Coast, Undated (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Bridge: Depoe Bay, Undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Bridge: Florence, Oregon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Bridge: Mill Creek, 1948 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 166)
- Bridge: Pontoon across Snake River near Pasco, Undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Bridge: Snake River during construction, 1951 April (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Bridge: Spokane, Undated (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Bridge: Unfinished: New highway on Oregon coast, Undated (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Bridges, Undated (Box 1, Folder 173)
- Bridges: Portland, Undated (Box 1, Folder 174)
- British Columbia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 175)
- British Columbia: Butchart Gardens, Undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
- Bronton, Ira: Fifty year wedding anniversary, Circa 1947 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Brooke Mountain, Undated (Box 1, Folder 177)
- Brotherton: Service Award, 1949 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Brotherton's Exteriors, 1947 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 181)
- Brotherton's Garage, 1947 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 182)
- Brotherton's Garage: Service Awards, 1949 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 183)
- Brotherton's Garage: Window Display, 1950 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 180)
- Broxon, 1948 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 184)
- Brunton: Anniversary, 1947 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 185)
- Buchanan and Bastron (Leroy) wedding, 1947 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Buckley, Undated (Box 1, Folder 187)
- Buckley, Undated (Box 1, Folder 188)
- Buckley, 1946 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 189)
- Buckley: Violin, Undated (Box 1, Folder 186)
- Bull Dogging: Dayton, Washington, 1942 May (Box 1, Folder 190)
- Bull, Brahma: Riding, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1778)
- Bus: 2nd and Main, Undated (Box 1, Folder 191)
- Butcher, Undated (Box 1, Folder 192)
- Butcher: Safeway, Circa 1942 (Box 1, Folder 193)
- Cabin: Log, Undated (Box 1, Folder 194)
- Cabin: Log: Copeland Place, Undated (Box 1, Folder 195)
- Cabin: Log: Lamar, Undated (Box 1, Folder 196)
- Cactus Garden: Santa Maria, California, Undated (Box 1, Folder 197)
- Cake, Wedding, Undated (Box 1, Folder 198)
- Calderon, Mrs.: At Soap Lake, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 199)
- Calf Roping: Dayton, 1942 May (Box 1, Folder 200)
- California: Palo Alto, Undated (Box 1, Folder 201)
- California: Pismo Beach, Undated (Box 1, Folder 202)
- Callow, Glen: Blue Mountain AVA and dust corp: Planes for paper cut, Undated (Box 1, Folder 203)
- Camp fire, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Campfire Girls, 1947 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 204)
- Campfire Girls: Walla Walla High School Gym, 1946 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 205)
- Camping: Bungalow, Undated (Box 1, Folder 206)
- Camping: Kooskooskie, Undated (Box 1, Folder 207)
- Camping: Lake Kachess, Undated (Box 1, Folder 208)
- Cancer Drive, 1946 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 209)
- Cannon Beach, Circa 1954 (Box 1, Folder 211)
- Cannon Beach and Ecola State Park, Circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 210)
- Cape Blanco, Circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 212)
- Cape Perpetua, Oregon, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1805)
- Car and Trailer, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Carlson, Pat, 1950 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 213)
- Carlson, Pat, 1950 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 214)
- Carnival: American United, Circa 1945 (Box 1, Folder 215)
- Carnival: American United: Tina Brown: Fat lady, Circa 1945 (Box 1, Folder 216)
- Carnival: Ferris, Undated (Box 1, Folder 218)
- Carnival: Walla Walla Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 217)
- Carrvel: State Line, 1947 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 219)
- Cat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 220)
- Cat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 221)
- Cat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 222)
- Cat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 223)
- Cat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 224)
- Cat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 225)
- Cat, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1775)
- Cat, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1780)
- Cat, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1781)
- Cat: On doorknob, 1946 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 226)
- Caterpillars, Undated (Box 1, Folder 227)
- Cattle and Calves, Circa 1951 (Box 1, Folder 230)
- Cattle and Dairy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 231)
- Cattle at Barn: Mill Creek, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 232)
- Cattle Grazing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 235)
- Cattle sale, 1948 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 241)
- Cattle show and sale, 1949 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 243)
- Cattle show and sale: Walla Walla, 1948 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 242)
- Cattle: Corson: Junior livestock show, 1947 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 238)
- Cattle: Dairy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 233)
- Cattle: Dairy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 234)
- Cattle: Hereford Prize Winner, 1946 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 236)
- Cattle: Hereford sale, 1947 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 239)
- Cattle: Hereford sale: Walla Walla, 1950 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 240)
- Cattle: Jersey, Undated (Box 1, Folder 237)
- Cattle: Second Annual show and sale, 1949 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Caver, Interior, Circa 1946 (Box 1, Folder 368)
- Caves: Oregon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 244)
- Cemetery: Frenchtown, Undated (Box 1, Folder 245)
- Certificate: Birth: Armstrong, Undated (Box 1, Folder 246)
- Chamber of Commerce: Meeting, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 247)
- Cherry Blossoms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 248)
- Cherry Blossoms, Undated (Box 1, Folder 249)
- Chickens Picking, 1940 December (Box 1, Folder 250)
- Children, Undated (Box 1, Folder 251)
- Children, Undated (Box 1, Folder 252)
- Children: Lacy bathing and Betty, Undated (Box 1, Folder 253)
- Children: Looking into back of camera, Undated (Box 1, Folder 254)
- Children: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Chinese [people], Undated (Box 1, Folder 255)
- Chinese girl: Dorothy Sue, Undated (Box 1, Folder 259)
- Chinese girls: On ferris wheel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 257)
- Chinese: Duquay, Undated (Box 1, Folder 256)
- Chinese: Peeling spuds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 258)
- Chipman, Harry B., 1951 September 15 (Box 1, Folder 260)
- Chipman, Mr. and Mrs.: Circus Inn: Yakima, Washington, Circa 1951 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Christmas Titles, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1809)
- Church banquet: Catholic sisters: Marcus Whitman: Lowden, Mrs. L.L., Norman Herring, 1946 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 261)
- Church: Catholic: Altar society, Undated (Box 1, Folder 228)
- Church: Catholic: Altar society: Mrs. Murphy at the home of Mrs. Ed Cochran, 1946 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 262)
- Church: Musicale: St. Vincent's Academy, 1946 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 263)
- Church: Seventh-Day Adventist: Walla Walla, 1946 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 265)
- Church: St. Paul's Episcopal Church: Mrs. King, Undated (Box 1, Folder 264)
- Church: United Brethren, Undated (Box 1, Folder 266)
- Circus, Undated (Box 1, Folder 311.01)
- Circus, Undated (Box 1, Folder 267)
- Circus, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Circus:, 1951 July (Box 1, Folder 300)
- Circus: 101 Ranch: Pendleton, Oregon, 1946 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 299)
- Circus: Arthur, 1943 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 311.02)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers, Circa 1945 (Box 1, Folder 268)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 311.07)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers:, Circa 1944 (Box 1, Folder 311.03)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers:, 1944 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 311.04)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers: Hobbs, John, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 311.18)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers: Horse troupe, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 311.19)
- Circus: Arthur Brothers: Mrs. Olvera, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 311.24)
- Circus: At Walla Walla Southeastern Fair, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 269)
- Circus: Beatty, 1947 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 271)
- Circus: Beatty, 1948 June 11 (Box 1, Folder 272)
- Circus: Beatty, 1949 June (Box 1, Folder 273)
- Circus: Beatty, Clyde, 1950 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 275)
- Circus: Beatty, Clyde, 1951 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 276)
- Circus: Cole, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 277)
- Circus: Cole Brothers, Circa 1942 (Box 1, Folder 283)
- Circus: Cole Brothers, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 285)
- Circus: Cole Brothers, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 311.1)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Beiler, Betty and pal, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 287)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Benson, Ginger "Kootz", Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 294)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Circus wagon America, Circa 1949 (Box 1, Folder 311.15)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Clown, Circa 1941 (Box 1, Folder 311.11)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Clown: McEvoy, H.F., Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 280)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Contortionist: Shubert, Joan, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 282)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Daily Brothers, Circa 1948 (Box 1, Folder 293)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Escalante, Betty on wagon tongue, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 288)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Fowler, Pat and Ballet, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 281)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Joy, Harper, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 311.12)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Maynard, Ken, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 279)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Mitchell versus Circus, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 290)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Mrs. Rich, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 311.13)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Old woman in the shoe, 1946 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 311.14)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Peanut Eater, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 291)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Rhino, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 292)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: The Antaleks: Balonce, Dale, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 286)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Thompson, Gladys and Bobby Donovan, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 289)
- Circus: Cole Brothers: Walla Walla and Pasco, 1946 August 17 (Box 1, Folder 284)
- Circus: Cole: Broadbent, Betty "Tattoo", Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 274)
- Circus: Cole: Conley, Kay "Kootz", Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 278)
- Circus: Contortionist: Shubert, John, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 311.16)
- Circus: Cowboy: Maynard, Ken, Circa 1940 (Box 1, Folder 311.22)
- Circus: Crowd, Undated (Box 1, Folder 311.17)
- Circus: Elephant and Girls: Beatty, Clyde, 1950 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 311.09)
- Circus: Elephants at fairgrounds: Beatty, Circa 1947 (Box 1, Folder 311.05)
- Circus: Group, Undated (Box 1, Folder 295)
- Circus: King Brothers, 1950 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 296)
- Circus: Laundry, Circa 1939 (Box 1, Folder 311.2)
- Circus: Lion, Undated (Box 1, Folder 311.21)
- Circus: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1, Folder 297)
- Circus: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1, Folder 311.23)
- Circus: Postcard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 311.25)
- Circus: R-B and B and B: Horses and trick riders, 1951 July (Box 1, Folder 311.26)
- Circus: Russel American, 1945 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 298)
- Circus: Russell Brother: Clowns, Circa 1944 (Box 1, Folder 311.08)
- Circus: Russell Brothers, Circa 1942 (Box 1, Folder 301)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: [Fat lady: Della Love], Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 306)
- Circus: Russell Brothers: Biel, Antes, Circa 1943 (Box 1, Folder 309.1)